const kaplanGreSynonymBank = [
    {
        question: "Abate",
        correct: "To reduce in amount, degree, or severity",
        description:"As the hurricane's force abated, the winds dropped the sea became calm.",
        synonyms:[
            "Ebb: to diminish; to recede",
            "Lapse: ",
            "Let up: ",
            "Moderate: ",
            "Relent: ",
            "Slacken: ",
            "Subside: to sink or settle; to diminish; to lessen",
            "Wane: to decrease in strength or intensity; to fade away; to decline in power"
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0001",
    },
    {
        question: "Banal",
        correct: "predictable, cliched, boring",
        description:"He used banal phrases like 'Have a nice Day' or 'Another day another dollar'.",
        synonyms:[
            "Bland: mild; tasteless; dull; unlively",
            "Bromidic: dull; ovious; overfamiliar saying",
            "Cliched: ",
            "Commonplace: ",
            "Fatuous: foolish; sily; idiotic",
            "Hackneyed: overused; trite; stale",
            "Innocuous: harmless; banal", 
            "Insipid: dull; bland; banal", 
            "Jejune: ", 
            "Musty: ",
            "Platitudinous: dull or trite remark; a cliche",
            "Prosaic: dull; unimaginative; like prose(as opposed to poetry)",
            "Quotidian: daily; everyday; ordinary",
            "Shopworn: ",
            "Stale: ",
            "Stereotypic: ",
            "Threadbare: ",
            "Timeworn: ",
            "Tired: ",
            "Trite: ",
            "Vapid: without liveliness; dull; spiritless",
            "Worn-out: "
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0002",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Capricious",
        correct: "changing one's mind quickly and often",
        description:"Queen Elizabeth I was capricious; her coutiers could never be sure which of their number would catch her fancy.",
        synonyms:[
            "Arbitary: random, capricious", 
            "Chance: ", 
            "Changeable: ", 
            "Erratic: (Wandering and unpredictable) The plot seemed predictable until it suddenly took a"+
            " series of erratic turns that surprised the audience.",
            "Errant: straying, mistaken, roving",
            "Fickle: likely to change for no good reason",
            "Inconstant: ",
            "Mercurial: emotionally unpredictable; rapidly changing in mood",
            "Random: ",
            "Whimsical: acting in a fanciful or capricious manner; unpredictable",
            "Willful: ",
            "Irresolute"
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0003",
    },
    {
        question: "Deference",
        correct: "respect, courtesy",
        description: "The respectful young law clerk treated the Supreme Court justice with the utmost deference.",
        synonyms:[
            "Courtesy: ", 
            "Homage: reverence", 
            "Obeisance: a bow or curtsy; deep reverence", 
            "Reverence: ",
            "Veneration: reverence",
            
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0004",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Enervate",
        correct: "To reduce in strength",
        description: "The guerrillas hoped that a series of surprise attacks would enervate the regular army.",
        synonyms:[
            "Unnerve: to deprive of strength or courage", 
            "Debilitate: to weaken; to cripple", 
            "Enfeeble: ", 
            "Sap: ",
            "Weaken: "
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0005",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Fanatical",
        correct: "Acting excessively enthusiastic",
        description: "The stomtroopers were fanatical in their devotion to the Emperor, readily sacrificing their lives for him.",
        synonyms:[
            "Extremist: ", 
            "Fiery: ", 
            "Frenzied: ", 
            "Zealous: "
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0006",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Garrulous",
        correct: "tending to talk a lot",
        description: "The garrulous parakeet distracted its owner with its continuous talking",
        synonyms:[
            "Effusive: ", 
            "Loquacious: ", 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0007",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Iconoclast",
        correct: "one who opposes established beliefs, customs, and institution",
        description: "His lack of regard for traditional belief soon established him as an iconoclast.",
        synonyms:[
            "Maverick: ", 
            "Nonconformist: ", 
            "Rebel: ", 
            "Revolutionary: "
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0008",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Malingerer",
        correct: "to evade responsibility by pretending to be ill",
        description: "A common way to avoid the draft was by malingering- pretending to be mentally or physically ill so as to avoid being taken by the army",
        synonyms:[
            "shirk: ", 
            "slack: ",  
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0009",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Naive",
        correct: "lacking sophistication or experience",
        description: "Having never traveled before, the hillbillies were more naive than the people they met in Beverly Hills",
        synonyms:[
            "Artless: ", 
            "Credulous: ", 
            "Guileless: ", 
            "Ingenuous: ",
            "Simple: "
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0010",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Obdurate",
        correct: "hardened in feeling; resistant to persuasion",
        description: "The president was completely obdurate on the issue, and amount of persuation would change his mind.",
        synonyms:[
            "Inflexible", 
            "Intransigent", 
            "Recalcitrant", 
            "Tenacious",
            "Unyielding"
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0011",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Paragon",
        correct: "Model of excellence or perfection",
        description: "She is the paragon of what a judge should be: honest, intelligent, hardworking, and just.",
        synonyms:[
            "Apotheosis", 
            "Ideal", 
            "Quintessence", 
            "Standard"
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0012",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Quiescent",
        correct: "motionless",
        description: "Many animals are quiescent over the winter months, minimizing activity in order to conserve energy.",
        synonyms:[
            "Dormant", 
            "Latent", 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0013",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Rarefy",
        correct: "to make thinner or sparser",
        description: "Since the atmosphere rarefy as altitudes increase, the air at the top of very tall mountains is too thin to breathe.",
        synonyms:[
            "Attenuate", 
            "Thin", 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0014",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Satiate",
        correct: "to satisfy fully or overindulge",
        description: "His desire for power was so great that nothing less than complete control of the country could satiate it.",
        synonyms:[
            "Sate: to fully satisfy or overindulge", 
            "Insatiable: incapable of being satisfied",
            "Cloy: ",
            "Glut: ",
            "Gorge: ",
            "Surfeit: " 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0015",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Transitory",
        correct: "temporary, lasting a brief time",
        description: "The reporter lived a transitory life, staying in one place only long enough to cover the current story.",
        synonyms:[
            "Transit: to pass through; to change or make a transition", 
            "Transient: passing quickly in and out of existence; one who stays a short time",
            "Ephemeral: ",
            "Evanescent: ",
            "Fleeting: ",
            "Imparmanent: ",
            "Momentary: " 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0016",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Vacillate",
        correct: "to sway physically; to be indecisive",
        description: "The customer held up the line as he vacillated between ordering chocolate chip or rocky road ice cream.",
        synonyms:[
            "Dither: ", 
            "Falter: ",
            "Fluctuate: ",
            "Oscillate: ",
            "Waver: " 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0017",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Whimsical",
        correct: "acting in a fanciful or capricious manner; unpredictable",
        description: "The ballet was whimsical, delighting the children with its imaginative characters and unpredictable sets.",
        synonyms:[
            "Whim: a fancy or sudden notion", 
            "Capricious: ",
            "Eratic: ",
            "Flippant: ",
            "Frivolous: " 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0018",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Zeal",
        correct: "passion, excitement",
        description: "She brought her typical zeal to the project, sparking enthusiasm in the other team members.",
        synonyms:[
            "Zealot: a fantic", 
            "Ardency: ",
            "Fervor: ",
            "Fire: ",
            "Passion: " 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0019",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Abscond",
        correct: "to leave secretly",
        description: "The patron absconded from the restaurant without paying his bill by sneaking out back door.",
        synonyms:[
            "Flee", 
            "Decamp",
            "Escape" 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0020",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Castigate",
        correct: "to punish or criticize harshly",
        description: "Americans are amazed at how harshly the authorities in Singapore castigate"+
        " perpetrators of what would be considered minor crimes in the United States.",
        synonyms:[
            "Admonish: ", 
            "Chastise",
            "Chide",
            "Rebuke",
            "Reprimand",
            "Reproach", 
            "Reprove",
            "Scold",
            "Tax",
            "Upbraid", 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0021",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Deride",
        correct: "to speak of or treat with contempt, to mock",
        description: "The awakward child was often derided by his cooler peers.",
        synonyms:[
            "Derision: mockery and taunts", 
            "Derisive: in a mocking manner",
            "Gibe: ", 
            "Jeer: ",
            "Mock",
            "Ridicule",
            "Scoff: ",
            "Sneer: ",
            "Taunt: " 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0022",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Enigma",
        correct: "a puzzle; a mystery",
        description: "Speaking in riddles and dressed in old robes, the artist gained a reputation as something of an enigma.",
        synonyms:[
            "Conundrum: ", 
            "Perplexity: " 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0023",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Fawn",
        correct: "to grovel; adulate",
        description: "The understudy fawned over the director in hopes of being cast in the part on a permanent basis.",
        synonyms:[
            "Bootlick: ", 
            "Grovel",
            "Pander", 
            "Toady", 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0024",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Gregarious",
        correct: "outgoing; sociable",
        description: "She was so gregarious that when she found herself alone she felt quite sad.",
        synonyms:[
            "Affable", 
            "Communicative",
            "Congenial", 
            "Sociable" 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0025",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Imperturbable",
        correct: "not capable of being disturbed",
        description: "The counselor had so much experience dealing with distraught children that ahe seemed imperturbable, "+
        "even when faced with the wildest tantrums.",
        synonyms:[
            "Perturb: to disturb greatly", 
            "Composed: ",
            "Dispassionate: ", 
            "Impassive: ",
            "Serene: ",
            "Stoical: ",
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0026",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Laconic",
        correct: "using few words",
        description: "She was a laconic poet who built her reputation on using words as sparingly as possible",
        synonyms:[
            "Concise", 
            "Curt",
            "Pithy", 
            "Taciturn",
            "Terse",
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0027",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Lament",
        correct: "to express sorrow; to grieve",
        description: "The children continued to lament the death of the goldfish weeks after its demise.",
        synonyms:[
            "Bewail: ", 
            "Deplore: ",
            "Grieve", 
            "Mourn",
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0028",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Malleable",
        correct: "capable of being shaped",
        description: "Gold is the most malleable of precious metals; it can easily be formed into almost any shape.",
        synonyms:[
            "Adaptable", 
            "Ductile",
            "Plastic", 
            "Pliable",
            "Pliant",
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0029",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Obsequious",
        correct: "overly submissive and eager to please",
        description: "The obsequious new associate made sure to compliment her supervisor's tie and agree with him on every issue.",
        synonyms:[
            "Obeisance: a physical show of respect or submission, such as a bow", 
            "Compliant",
            "Deferential", 
            "Servile",
            "Subservient",
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0030",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Pedant",
        correct: "someone who shows off learning",
        description: "The graduate instructor's tedious and excessive commentary on the subject soon gained her a reputation as pedant.",
        synonyms:[
            "Pedantic: making an excessive display of learning",  
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0031",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Repudiate",
        correct: "to reject the validity of",
        description: "The old woman's claim that she was Russian royalty was repudiated when DNA tests showed she was of no relation to them.",
        synonyms:[
            "Deny", 
            "Disavow",
            "Disclaim",
            "Disown",
            "Renounce" 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0032",    
    },
    {
        question: "Soporific",
        correct: "causing sleep or lethargy",
        description: "The movie proved to be so soporific that soon loud snores were heard throughout the theater.",
        synonyms:[
            "Sopor: deep sleep", 
            "Hypnotic",
            "Narcotic",
            "Slumberous",
            "Somnolent" 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0033",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Tirade",
        correct: "long, harsh speech or verbal attack",
        description: "Observers were shocked at the manager's tirade over such a minor mistake.",
        synonyms:[
            "Diatribe", 
            "Fulmination",
            "Harangue",
            "Obloquy",
            "Revilement",
            "Vilification",
            "Invective",
            "Jeremiad",
            "Malediction", 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0034",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Veracity",
        correct: "truthfulness, accuracy",
        description: "She had a reputation for veracity, so everyone trusted her description of events.",
        synonyms:[
            "Verity: truth", 
            "Veracious: filled with truth and accuracy",
            "Candor",
            "Exactitude",
            "Fidelity",
            "Probity" 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0035",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Abstain",
        correct: "to choose not to do something",
        description: "During Lent, practicing Catholics abstain from eating meat.",
        synonyms:[
            "Forbear", 
            "Refrain",
            "Withhold",
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0036",
    },
    {
        question: "Abyss",
        correct: "an extremly deep hole",
        description: "The submarine dove into the abyss to chart the previously unseen depths.",
        synonyms:[
            "Abyssal: pertaining to great depth", 
            "Abysmal: extremely bad",
            "Chasm", 
            "Void",
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0037",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Bolster",
        correct: "to support; to prop up",
        description: "The presence of giant footprints bolstered the argument that Sasquatch was in the area.",
        synonyms:[
            "Brace", 
            "Buttres",
            "Prop",
            "Support", 
            "Sustain",
            "Underpin",
            "Uphold"
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0038",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Bombastic",
        correct: "pompous in speech and manner",
        description: "Mussolini's speeches were mostly bombastic; his boasting and outrageous claims had no basis in fact.",
        synonyms:[
            "Bombast:pompas speech or writing", 
            "Bloated",
            "Declamatory", 
            "Fustain",
            "Grandiloquent",
            "Grandiose",
            "High-flown",
            "Magliloquent",
            "Orotund",
            "Pretentious",
            "Rhetorical",
            "Self-important", 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0039",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Cacophony",
        correct: "harsh; jarring noise",
        description: "The junior high orchestra created an almost unbearable cacophony as they tried to tune their instruments.",
        synonyms:[
            "Chaos", 
            "Clamor",
            "Din",
            "Discord", 
            "Disharmony",
            "Noise",

        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0040",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Candid",
        correct: "impartial and honest in speech",
        description: "The observations of a child can be charming since they are candid and unpretentious.",
        synonyms:[
            "Direct", 
            "Forthright",
            "Frank", 
            "Honest",
            "Open",
            "Sincere",
            "Straight",
            "Straightforward",
            "Undisguised" 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0041",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Desultory",
        correct: "jumping from one thing to another; disconnected",
        description: "Diane had a desultory academic record; she had changed majors 12 times in three years.",
        synonyms:[
            "Aimless", 
            "Erratic",
            "Haphazard",
            "Indiscriminate", 
            "Objectless",
            "Purposeless",
            "Random",
            "Stray",
            "Unconnected",
            "Unplanned"
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0042",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Diffident",
        correct: "lacking self-confidence",
        description: "Steve's diffident manner during the job interview stemmed from his nervous nature and lack of experience in the field.",
        synonyms:[
            "Backword", 
            "Bashful",
            "Demure", 
            "Modest",
            "Coy",
            "Retiring",
            "Self-effacing",
            "Shy" 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0043",
        
    },
    {
        question: "",
        correct: "",
        description: "",
        synonyms:[
            "", 
            "",
            "",
            "", 
            "",
            "",

        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0015",
        
    },
    {
        question: "",
        correct: "",
        description: "",
        synonyms:[
            "", 
            "",
            "", 
            "",
            "", 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0015",
        
    },
    {
        question: "",
        correct: "",
        description: "",
        synonyms:[
            "", 
            "",
            "",
            "", 
            "",
            "",

        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0015",
        
    },
    {
        question: "",
        correct: "",
        description: "",
        synonyms:[
            "", 
            "",
            "", 
            "",
            "", 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0015",
        
    },
    {
        question: "",
        correct: "",
        description: "",
        synonyms:[
            "", 
            "",
            "",
            "", 
            "",
            "",

        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0015",
        
    },
    {
        question: "",
        correct: "",
        description: "",
        synonyms:[
            "", 
            "",
            "", 
            "",
            "", 
        ],
        answers: [ "", "", "", ""],
        questionId: "0015",
        
    },
    
]


export default (n = 5) =>
        Promise.resolve(kaplanGreSynonymBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
    